(Sheldon:)I wonder what they're talking about.
PENNY: If you guys
(Penny:)would shut up,
I could tell you.
(Howard:)Oh.
(Penny:)Be cool, be cool, be cool.
(Attorney:)Hey.
(Raj:)Hello.
Hey. You guys all right?
(Howard:)Yeah. But, um, we were talking,
(Howard:)and... I'm a
little concerned
(Howard:)about the three of us
forming a partnership.
(Sheldon:)Are you suggesting
a limited liability corporation?
'Cause I did not
L-L-see that coming.
(Howard:)Sheldon, my concern is not
with the money or anything.
It's-it's with
how you treat me.
(Sheldon:)Well, I believe I'm
treating you generously.
(Sheldon:)That's why I've stipulated
in the contract
(Sheldon:)that your contributions
to our invention
(Sheldon:)are as valuable as my own.
(Bernadette:)Are you saying
that his contributions
(Bernadette:)aren't as valuable
as yours?
(Sheldon:)No, I am not saying that,
(Sheldon:)because I kept saying
that this morning
(Sheldon:)and Leonard said,
“Stop saying that.”
(Howard:)See? This is what happens
every time we work together.